http://www.tanisinc.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Tanis will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transmit, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING
Tanis is the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. Tanis will not sell or rent this information to anyone and will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
ACCESS AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION
You may opt out of any future Tanis contacts at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.
SECURITY
At Tanis, we take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline through encryption and secure transmittal lines. We also protect your information offline, with only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Tanis Brush Incorporated 3660 Kettle Court East | Delafield, WI 53018 Phone 262.646.9000 | Fax 262.646.9005 Toll Free: 800.234.7002 [email protected]
© 2020 Tanis Brush. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy | Site: Marketing Metrics Corp.
